

CONTACT

t. +94 77 5921 375

315/A, Helan Mawatha Wennappuwa

mbnuwantha90@gmail.com

github.com/MadukaNuwantha

linkedin.com/in/madukanuwantha

SKILLS

Programing Langauages

- Dart
- Java
- Java Script
- HTML
- CSS

Databases

- MongoDB
- Firebase
- MYSOL

Frameworks & Tools

- Flutter
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- VueJS
- VS Code
- GIT
- Postman
- Bit Bucket
- Android Studio

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Quick Learner
- Leadership
- Self Motivated
- Ability to work in collaboration

Maduka Nuwantha

Software Developer

Innovative Software engineer with an experience of facilitating advanced engineering solutions with a wide range of software applications and technological skills. Expert in mobile application development methodologies, tools and processes. Recognized as a corporative, well-organized and logically thinking employee in a fast paced, deadline driven environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer 2022/09 - Present

Share Colombo Services

Associate Software Developer 2022/03 - 2022/09

Share Colombo Services

Software Developer Intern 2021/09 - 2022/03

Share Colombo Services

PROJECTS

Work Projects

Aventage CRM

Share Colombo Services

Flutter

xVer

Share Colombo Services

Flutter

University Projects

Teacher Rating App

Flutter, NodeJS

Online Computer Store

ReactJS, NodeJS, MongoDB

Animal Shelter Management System

VueJS, NodeJS, MongoDB

Company Management System

VueJS, NodeJS, MongoDB

Cargills App Clone

Healthy Life Style

Share Colombo Services

Flutter

Flutter

Fuel Management System

Java (Android), Node JS, Mongo DB

Online Conference Management System

VueJS, NodeJS, MongoDB

Deforestation Monitoring System

Python, Fast API, Node JS, React JS

EDUCATION

BSc. (Hons) in Software Engineering

Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology

GCE Advance Level - 2018

St. Peter's College - Colombo 04 Negombo Branch

REFERENCES

Amalka Perera

Entrepreneur Phone: 0772204028

Email: amalka74@yahoo.com